xtratheme.com 2014-04-13

# Privacy Policy - Xtratheme

**Xtratheme.com Privacy Policy**  
At Xtratheme, we have created this privacy statement in order to show our commitment to your privacy. In general, we respect your privacy here at Xtratheme.com and we will never give away your contact information without your prior consent and approval. This page discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the website Xtratheme.com.

**Information Gathering**  
As with most other websites, we automatically collect and utilize the data contained in our site log files. The information in the log files will include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP, browser used (IE, Firefox, Safari, etc…), the date and time you visited our site and which URLs you visited throughout our site. We track your activity with Google Analytics, Quantcast, and WordPress Analytics.

**Advertising**  
We run our own advertising system which does not utilize cookies. Some of our advertisers may choose to host their own advertisement, and could thus use it set a cookie for tracking purposes. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by their respective owners, and we do not have access to this information. Cookies are used on Xtratheme only for login, commenting, and other related community purposes.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites including in some cases, affiliate links. Xtratheme.com and it’s authors are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Please refer to the destination website policies for such information

**Personal Information**  
When you comment or subscribe to an email list, we will ask for your name, email address and optionally website. When you register on the site or when you sign up for special events, webcasts, or whitepapers, we may request additional info. Your email and other information may be used for contacting you about updates to Xtratheme and if requested, for our newsletters. Your  **personal information will not be distributed  **to anyone for any purpose unless clearly designated as such, and with your opt-in and approval. This site complies with all rules and requirements of the [CAN-SPAM Act](http://transition.fcc.gov/cgb/consumerfacts/canspam.html)

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at the following page: [About us](http://xtratheme.com/about).
